What comes to your mind
when you hear the words
Road Trip?
Hangover
Zindagi Na Milegi Dobara
Dil Chahta Hai
Basically friends...
Rocking it
Baba, what are you doing?
Bastard
But would you ever
consider doing
A road trip with your siblings?
Road Trip with brother and sister?
It could be fun, you know.
Baba, mind your language!
Ah! You're choking me!
Let go my hair, you ass.
Baba, I was worried about you.
Baba, you're an animal!
You have betrayed me!
Hey, that's your car!
What the fuck!
What stupidity is this?
Did Chanchal take the car?
I doubted her ever since my childhood.
Hey!
You're the one who looks like a thief.
I was watching your pansy fight
RV isn't there too!
Oh, shit!
Oh, fuck!
Baba, I'm so sorry.
Shut it down and raise the
volume of this match!
Chitvan...
Extremely talented and I
really love your music
But these guys clearly don't
Everyone will dance once
the match gets over.
Now lower the volume
and play the pen-drive
Take a break.
Baba?
Hey, Chitvan. You're here
Baba, this is such a surprise...
Watch it, man. You're
peeing on my shoe.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I got excited.
What are you doing here?
Taking a piss.
I mean, here, in the club.
I came to meet you.
Bombay? What are you
doing in India?
I sent you an e-mail.
Was waiting at the airport since 5.
Finally, decided to come by myself.
Baba...
I check emails after 11:45 a.m.
on Mondays
Divorce?
When did you get  married?
What drugs are you on?
Weren't you living with that
foreigner boss of yours?
Yes.
Whom did you marry?
Same woman.
But wasn't she quite elder to you?
So?
When did you marry?
6 months back.
You didn't even invite me!
Are you a fool?
We talked on the phone.
You congratulated me.
We had a Skype chat.
Oh, really?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Are you done?
Because I got done.
I'm just giving
you some company.
Baba, it's so nice to see you!
What are you doing?
Wash your hands.
He's told me this much, dad.
I'll call you once I
know the details.
Yeah, alright
Okay. Bye.
Don't spill any of this to the parents.
Sure.
Compatibility is...
A bitch.
Love and stuff is still simple
But tuning.
That's important.
Because if you want two
different things in life,
It fucking never works.
They tend to dominate
Yeah, man.
Take it to their ego
Handcuffs
Using hunters and all
Ike the entire womanhood is taking revenge
for 50 shades of Grey.
What are you saying?
You were telling about
Domination and sexually powerful position
I suggest that from the very beginning,
Show her who's boss in bed.
Shut her up right there.
I'm not talking about my sex life.
It's general compatibility.
You're so dumb!
Oh!
Your sex life was sorted?
My sex life?
I'm your elder brother, you fool.
She's your in-law.
Was.
Was my in-law.
I've accepted it. You should, too.
Baba,
Drink.
Be right back.
Compatibility...
is a bitch.
Love and all gets managed.
But tuning.
That's vital.
Then if you want two
different things in life
Compatibility
It all comes down to that.
What do you mean?
Where should I take him
in this condition?
He's your brother,
not some stray dog, bro.
He came to you
directly from America.
What are you talking about?
Obviously, you have
to take him with you.
Yeah, that was insensitive of me, no?
But I'm not habitual
of having him around
Yeah, but
Family stands by you in times of crisis.
Where are we?
About to reach Navsari.
Gujarat border, baba.
If you need any booze then let's
pick it up. You won't find it ahead.
Gujarat border.
Yup.
Why?
Road Trip.
Don't blabber shit, Chitvan.
Where are we going?
Jodhpur.
To Chanchal's.
Chanchal's?
Yup.
Why?
Baba
But my life is fucked.
I can't take care of myself.
How will I manage you?
It's best that you stay with Chanchal.
But I don't want to go
to her place right now.
going to Manali to
meet mom and dad.
Why would I stay at my
sister's in-laws' place?
Why didn't you take
me to your place?
I did.
Things went south there.
You were drunk
I, somehow, put you
in the car and
Put you to sleep.
There was some disturbance
And I saw some people there for extortion
Loan sharks.
To collect last six months' EMIs
Will they take my car just
because some 5-6 checks bounced?
You should disappear.
Will have to leave Bombay.
Pakistan!
Maharashtra border, fool.
So I decided to take you to Chanchal.
So you're on the run?
You make it sound like I'm on
the run with someone else's car.
A little.
I'll pay the rest.
You got a lot of money?
Yeah, a lot.
Got it in divorce settlement.
She was culpable for the
affair so I got the money.
Oh, man.
You should have told me earlier.
I paid for your alcohol last night.
We're not discussing my problems here.
We're trying to clear
the mess in your life.
Let's go to Bombay
and solve your problem.
I'll handle my issues
once I've dealt with you.
Don't worry about me, boss.
Alright.
We'll reach Baroda in 3 hours.
Take a flight from there.
Pass me the keys.
Why?
You're having herbs instead
of tea this early in
What are you doing in life?
What?
What's the plan?
Running away from your place
like a thief because of money
Baba, don't ruin my high  by lecturing me.
Right.
Always stay high.
Live life from one moment to the next.
There's no focus, you don't
have any plans for your life
Baba, you had a plan, right?
Going well?
No, you're  right.
My plans failed.
My fucking marriage has failed
I'm jobless, homeless.
Thanks.
There's a plan
Breakfast.
There's a mind blowing place
to eat a little ahead.
Excuse me.
Could you please tell me how far Bharuch
is by checking it on the internet?
Yeah, sure.
The connection is a little weak here.
Where are you going anyway?
Baroda.
That'll do too.
Doesn't it get
Hot in this suit?
Yeah, it gets hot but
I'm habitual now.
Do you have any
other bad habits?
You should ask someone
inside about Bharuch
That'd be better.
At the reception...
What was that?
She was hitting on you.
Exactly but why?
Why so modest?
You're beautiful, Baba.
And women can smell broken marriages
and money quicker than a dog.
Let's go?
No, due to all this...
Dad was asking.
You told Dad?
Yeah, had to discuss plans for Jodhpur.
You told them about Jodhpur too?
I couldn't take such a big decision alone.
Texted Chanchal too.
Come on, man.
You should have told me once.
Now she'll feel bad if we don't go.
No one's gonna feel bad.
Everyone is busy in their lives.
Call Chanchal up.
Greetings, sir.
Yes, sir. Sure, sir.
Chanchal's gonna be a mother.
Chanchal's pregnant?
Means I'm gonna become a Chacha(uncle)
Chacha? It's your
sister's child.
Fuck man!
Chacha sounds so much better.
You took this from me too!
Chachu...Chachu...
Fuck you.
I think we should go to Jodhpur.
I've been saying
that for so long.
I always wanted to be like my dad.
But
Life has today made me a Maama.
Used to plan everything.
Sleeping on time,
Waking up on time,
Eating on time.
He used to decide Sunday's food on Friday.
I also did the same.
But the one thing my dad wouldn't plan
Were his road trips.
Every year, we used to go on
road trips for family holidays.
Always unplanned.
Just took the luggage and left.
Kashmir some time,
Some time Sikkim
Or Kerala
Or Rajasthan.
Chitvan...
Is like Dad on road trips.
Whom I could never understand.
Even you don't know!
That's a surprise.
Yeah, I'll call you once
I know the entire thing.
Okay, bye.
Dad also doesn't know.
Might not have told everyone
because of it being too soon.
There's a party for pregnancy,
Let's go.
Chanchal turned to be really smart.
Her life is set.
I don't understand the
need to do all this.
Is it necessary to celebrate
every other thing?
Bhabhi, these are delicate matters.
It's difficult to say anything.
You never know...
Chandan!
Chanchal.
Chitvan.
Elephant.
You look shocked. But didn't
he send you a message?
Earlier today
On which number?
9872534...
Chitvan,
That's not my number.
Sent it to Chanchal Chabra again.
Fuck.
You didn't tell that you were pregnant?
How do you know?
Why are you here?
Baba was taking a break
after his divorce.
Came to my club
while I was peeing...
You never told me that
you had a divorce.
I didn't know about
the marriage too.
What? Told you while we were peeing...
Bhabhi, you go ahead.
I'll be there in a couple of minutes.
Namaste.
You didn't even tell mom and dad?
No no no...
Oh.
What?
Chitvan.
Camel!
About my divorce, your pregnancy
He can't keep anything in his stomach.
Baba, communication is really important.
Don't you see how
dysfunctional have we become?
No no no no...
Fuck!
There's a problem!
What happened?
I'm not actually pregnant.
What the fuck?
What is all this? These flowers?
All this decoration?
I just said it
Make these people quiet.
It was a small lie.
Pranav went and told everybody.
Now, what?